{
  "data": [
        {
            "question": "The film was about a man who was sent to prison for _____ crime he didn't commit.",
            "a": "a",
            "b": "an",
            "c": "the",
            "d": "-",
            "answer": "1",
            "explain": "\n- A: used to show that you are talking about someone or something that has not been mentioned before, or that your listener does not know about",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "7"
        },
        {
            "question": "Most _____ animals in this zoo are fed twice a day.",
            "a": "a",
            "b": "an",
            "c": "the",
            "d": "-",
            "answer": "4",
            "explain": "\n- Omission of Articles: If common noun is in the form of plural noun, it will not take any",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "7"
        },
        {
            "question": "Martin likes badminton, but he doesn't often get ______ chance to play.",
            "a": "a",
            "b": "an",
            "c": "the",
            "d": "-",
            "answer": "3",
            "explain": "\n - Use \"the\": enough of something for a particular purpose",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "7"
        },
        {
            "question": "A: Have you seen ______ children?\nB: They are playing in the garden, I think.",
            "a": "a",
            "b": "an",
            "c": "the",
            "d": "-",
            "answer": "3",
            "explain": "\n- Omission of Articles: If common noun is in the form of plural noun, it will not take any ",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "7"
        },
        {
            "question": "_____ history was Colin's favourite subject at school.",
            "a": "a",
            "b": "an",
            "c": "the",
            "d": "-",
            "answer": "4",
            "explain": "\n- Omission of Articles: Names of academic subjects: mathematics, biology, history, computer science",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "7"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don't like _____ people who talk while they are eating. I think it is bad manners.",
            "a": "a",
            "b": "an",
            "c": "the",
            "d": "-",
            "answer": "4",
            "explain": "\n- Omission of Articles: If common noun is in the form of plural noun, it will not take any ",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "7"
        },
        {
            "question": "That was _____ great meal. I thought the steak was excellent.",
            "a": "a",
            "b": "an",
            "c": "the",
            "d": "-",
            "answer": "1",
            "explain": "\n- A: used before nouns that are usually uncountable when other information about the quality, feeling etc is added by an adjective, phrase, orclause",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "7"
        },
        {
            "question": "Nicholas is interested in _____ music. He has a huge collection of CDs.",
            "a": "a",
            "b": "an",
            "c": "the",
            "d": "-",
            "answer": "4",
            "explain": "\n- Do not use article when we mention something in general",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "7"
        },
        {
            "question": "The cake Angela made was great but I didn't like _____ coffee very much.",
            "a": "a",
            "b": "an",
            "c": "the",
            "d": "-",
            "answer": "3",
            "explain": "\n- Use \"the\": when you are about to make it clear which person or thing you mean ",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "7"
        },
        {
            "question": "A: Where did you get _____ flowers from?\nB: I bought them when I was shopping in town. Aren't they beautiful!",
            "a": "a",
            "b": "an",
            "c": "the",
            "d": "-",
            "answer": "3",
            "explain": "\n- Use \"the\": when you are about to make it clear which person or thing you mean\n",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "7"
        }
    ]
}